<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>0&#39;s and 1&#39;s!</title>
    <description>The bits of my life.</description>
    <link>http://kkcorps.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://kkcorps.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 17:45:04 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 17:45:04 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Guess What! I&#39;m Blogging Again.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;People who are friends with me on Facebook are perfectly aware of the fact that I go on a status marathon whenever I&#39;ve vacations.But this time, I&#39;m taking that up a notch and so, tada!!, I present to you my new blog where I&#39;ll be pouring my heart out during these two months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;But why a blog?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past few months, some really screwed up decisions led me to some place (known as Gurgaon) other than where most of my friends have landed.My friends would die without me and this blog will also serve to rejoice them these two months.Below is the collage of bunch of idiots (who are doing much better than me so I don&#39;t know what that makes me) I hang out with.Btw, kakul why I don&#39;t have a pic with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/about-bg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Me and my friends&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since memories are the only constant in this ever changing worlds (I know it&#39;s not scientifically true CR/Dwivedi/Mathur so don&#39;t even say that), I hope this blog will create some memeories for all of us and will be the right way to begin a story that will never end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;So what about the old one?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ohh I completely forgot about that!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just Kidding, actually my old &lt;a href=&quot;https://kkcrps.blogspot.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; got cluttered with a lot of nonsensical posts and so I thought of starting from scratch.Also, having your own site is way much cooler.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;section-heading nope&quot;&gt;Anything else?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not really but since I don&#39;t have much to do right now here&#39;s a poem for you
&lt;blockquote&gt;Roses are red,&lt;br /&gt;
Sky is blue,&lt;br /&gt;
Click &lt;a href=&quot;.nope&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; for more,&lt;br /&gt;
Ya I got you&lt;br /&gt;
HAHAHA...&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I bid you farewell for now.&lt;br /&gt;
Till my next post,&lt;br /&gt;
Sayo Nara&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 21:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://kkcorps.github.io/2015/05/14/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://kkcorps.github.io/2015/05/14/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
